

Profile

Skilled .NET software developer with over 10 years' experience.

Developed and implemented over 15 software products from concept to production. Constantly working to improve my skills and knowledge. Willing to work remotely under a B2B contract or in a Polish office.

Skills

- C#, C++, Java, Swift
- WPF, MVVM
- Windows Forms
- SwiftUI
- Silverlight, WCF RIA Services
- Android SDK
- Multithreading
- ASP.NET Core, Web API
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- ADO.NET, SQL queries
- Entity Framework
- MS SQL, Sybase
- NUnit
- TFS, GIT

Education

Polotsk State University Faculty of Information Technology Software Engineer 2009

Languages

- Russian Native
- English B1

ANDREI BRYZINSKI

.NET Software Developer

Phone

+375 29 7186284

+48 452 868 376

Email

admin@botbeetle.com

G

Postal Address

Warszawa, al. Jana Pawla II, nr 43A, lok. 37B, 01-001

Experience

.NET Software Developer, Full time SoftVec. Belarus, Minsk

01.2016 - Present

Participate in the development of a trading and analysis programme that trades shares on the Morgan Stanley exchange. The client is a private fund. Trading volume - millions of dollars.

- Provided reception, processing and display of trading data from IQFeed, Nanex feeds (C#, TCP/IP);
- Developed genetic algorithm for trading strategy research (C#, WinForm);
- Imported and stored stock data (C#, SQL);
- Developed charts for reporting (C#, WPF);
- Developed a Morgan Stanley stock market simulator as a TCP/IP server to test trading strategies without a real connection (C#, WinForm, TCP/IP, SQL);
- Developed a data TCP/IP server that works with large amounts of data. It
 downloads and stores trading data on a daily basis to allow quick access for
 trading strategies (C#, WinForm, TCP/IP, SQL).

.NET Software Developer, Free time

07.2012 - Present

Individual entrepreneur

Designed, developed and continue to maintain the trading application for Betfair.com, the world's largest sports betting exchange. Certified. Over 8,000 unique users, over 1,000 access subscriptions sold. Website www.botbeetle.com

- Windows application version (C#, WinForm, WPF);
- MacOS application version (Swift, SwiftUI);
- User and subscription management website (C#, Asp.net Core, MS SQL).

.NET Software Developer, Remote

04.2017 - 09.2017

Radar. Belarus, Minsk

Designed, developed and implemented complex software for a radio monitoring centre based on a digital map as part of automated operator workstations (GIS, C#, WinForm, TCP/IP) and a data server (C#, MS SQL, TCP/IP). Performed mathematical calculations on the propagation of radio waves and displayed the results on a map (GIS, C#, WinForm) and on a tablet (Swift, Android SDK).

.NET Software Developer, Full time

11.2013 - 12.2015

BerlioSoft. Belarus, Minsk

The largest company in Belarus providing cashless payment options at petrol stations (800 locations). I have designed and implemented the following projects:

- Web-based Silverlight application for the company's call centre, which handles contract registration for new customers (C#, Silverlight, WPF, WCF RIA Services, Sybase);
- Web service that connects to telecom operators and allows sending SMS messages to the company's customers (C#, WebService);
- Website that provides customers with information about payments, account balance, petrol station locations and more (ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, JavaScript);
- Android application with similar functionality to the website. (Java, Android SDK, C#, Web Service);
- Android applications for cash register and barcode scanning (Java, Android SDK, C#, C++, Web Service).